[__] I just sliced my hand I actually
did just but who gives up [__] good
morning ladies and gentlemen welcome to
week 11 turning $100 into a
million all I can say is let me let my
results speak for
themselves now you might be wondering
what the [__] the video just started it
didn't the video started yesterday on
Sunday swings welcome welcome welcome to
another Sunday swings where I literally
broke down every single one of these
trades to the tee I started off
yesterday Sunday swings not only
explaining the difficulties that I was
going through on the hundred to the mill
there's nothing you can do you can have
the most motivation you could possibly
ever ask for to actually be able to go
catch the fish but if the
don't give you the opportunities to go
fish there's nothing that you can do
about it but how I was not going to let
that affect my trading and how I was
still going to come into this new week
with this with this same mindset that I
had up to this point in the challenge
and how my actual strategy nothing's
wrong with it the only thing that
happened is the trader behind the
strategy he was simply [__] up so not
only did I do that but I also shared the
pairs that I was going to be trading USD
CAD nzd JP everything will pop up the
Clips here for you guys so USD CAD we're
looking at into very soon just going to
wait for a little Wick to the upside USD
JPY we currently have a weekly body
retest at previous weekly structure
points K JPY is another trade that we're
interested in next AUD JPY is quite
literally the exact same thing so
gbpusd is going to be I'd say
technically my second pair that I'm
interested for the week because this is
my number one pair and then all of these
pairs are technically my number two
because they're all identical and early
last night I did it I entered USD CAD on
the sales once again so if you guys go
watch last week's series you guys would
see what I went through last week right
here at this very moment I entered this
trade got stopped out at break even I
closed out at break even I entered this
trade closed myself out of break even
right here it was an absolute brutal
Friday now price came back into the area
did exactly what I said it was going to
do and then we executed the positions
right at the top of this area such a
beautiful trade look at this retest here
from this level of support support
support resistance rejection from the
EMA daily time frame currently having
that break of structure this daily
Candlestick can go off 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9
10 11 candlesticks then we had the
pullback then we had the weekly double
doy rejection from the EMA rejection
from the structure like there's so many
things that are going to make this trade
create a new lower low rather than
create a higher high all I did was
simply reenter the trade where I was
originally entered the only thing that
changed is the mindset behind when I
enter this trade versus when I entered
this trade but if you notice I'm taking
the exact same trade look at the pattern
formation here and where it is it's at
the area of Interest EMA look at the
pattern formation here it's at the area
of Interest and EMA and then you simply
set and forgets and we are now up
$168,000 and yes it's the same account
as always boys you guys can see right
here in the trade history we can like I
can literally close this position right
now so it's literally Monday morning and
I can literally close out this position
at this very point right here and be
done for the week and there goes this
series 10 5 minutes but you know what
we're not stopping there we're going to
keep it going we're going to try and
turn this 100 something thousand into
the million today probably not let's be
realistic
so I am literally about to close this
position at any given moment probably
about to close this position because the
4H hour is indeed having a rejection
from the structure point which it is my
first takeprofit right at this structure
point but the downside Potential from
this trade from here is absolutely
ridiculous so let me just explain to you
the other markets that I am interested
in before we close this one at $160,000
in profit we were just up 170 and we
just lost 10,000 talking [__] so next
Market that I am interested in in is
going to be USD JPY where we're going to
be waiting for a break and retest to
then sell to the downside so we had the
break the retest now we're kind of
waiting on that
rejection CAD JPY no break and retest no
trade Euro JPY no break and retest no
trade AUD JPY we're waiting for a break
and retest to then sell nzdjpy we're
waiting for a break and retest to then
sell no break no retest gbpusd we're
waiting for a retest of this area to
then buy but the market has not given us
the retest how we wanted it to it kind
of had a halfast pullback and we're
waiting for it to actually make it and
retest this EMA to then go to the upside
and then USD CHF we're going to be
waiting for price to have a solid break
above this area then a retest and then
we'll continue heading to the upside so
USD cat as of right
now there's our there's our girl right
here a [__]
oh [__] now we're up 157 fantastic great
okay all right I'm I'm going to
determine in the next 15 minutes if we
should like look at that would you want
to close after humongous bearish
rejection candles St like that we're
going to wait another 6 minutes to
decide exactly what we're going to do on
this position so let's wait all right
boys trade update we are currently up
189 so I just explained to you guys that
we have to wait for the 15-minute
Candlestick to close
and imagine if we would have closed
right here at 150 and then this happened
literally couple seconds after like you
guys need to understand this is the
whole point of set and forget when you
enter a winning position it's to set and
forget it's to not close your profit
short last week when I was telling you
guys that this trade had a down a big
time downside potential when we were in
this position right here and you guys
were telling me Oh you need to close
when this trade was at this point right
here literally this Market was at this
point and I was up about $100,000 at
this point pop up the clip so people can
have some context if it's their first
time seeing it
$50,000 wor a balance of
$91,000 this trade has the potential to
be A4 million so let me show you guys
right here so earlier we were obviously
anticipating for price to have a body
Candlestick closure under this level and
if we did we were golden but price is
having a pullback to now retest this
level of support support support and
then resistance through here when it was
this point you guys were saying yo close
the trade close the trade you're up 100K
and and it's what I'm telling you guys
like you guys are looking at the money
I'm not I don't care that I'm up 100K
the trade is not done the trade has to
be closed at a minimum of a one to two
risk reward if I were to have closed
this trade at this point right here I
would have Clos at a 1 to
1.2 I have to close at a minimum a 1 to2
RIS reward now yes I'm up 100K at this
point is that crazy for sure but I'm
breaking my trading plan if I don't let
it hit my take profit I have the weekly
in my favor I have the daily in my favor
I have the 4H hour in my favor I have
all the price action I can possibly ask
for in my favor for this trade to to go
to the downside why would I do an
impulsive close for 100k when I see the
downside potential of the trade I'm
following my trading plan if I set and
forget if I close early that is why I'm
being emotional now that we understand
that that me being up 100K and not
closing there doesn't mean that I am
being greedy I'm following my trading
plan clearly my trading plan worked
because I did not lose this trade at any
point if I would have contined to set
and forget this trade was only
technically lost because I manually
closed this trade and I manually closed
this trade but if I would have continued
to set and forget this one and this one
look where we would be right now the
analysis was was correct the only issue
is the trader behind this analysis was
incorrect now if I decide that we are at
a 1 to three risk reward on this trade
to not close at this point now I'm being
greedy because now the trade has hit the
point where I wanted to hit the analysis
has played out but for whatever reason I
want more profits this is not enough now
if I don't close right now with in total
profit
$195,000 now I'm being greedy now I'm
breaking my trading plan because the
trade has indeed played out and I have
gotten the trade that I wanted to but
keep in mind this trade still has so
much more downside potential this trade
we have just retested this let me let me
remove this little Clos thing has just
retested this strong level of support
and this strong level of resistance with
the EMA last time we broke and retested
this point here look at the massive move
that we had we have to minimum set our
take profit right back down at this
level I'm setting my take profit right
at this structure level because it is
the first and closest point that the
market can have a reaction from but the
real takeprofit that we have to have is
this one now obviously because we're in
the challenge and you know I need to be
a little bit more realistic with the
results I'm probably not going to be
holding for that long but this trade has
so much more downside potential that all
I'm doing by holding is stay scking to
the plan I am not being greedy I need
you guys to understand that really
comprehend that because by me simply set
and forgetting I am maximizing the
profits that I am analyzing I am
analyzing a margin a market like
literally let's put it like this I am
analyzing a market major shift of move
right so if we're over here and we have
a shift of structure and then we retest
here I'm literally entering the trade
here and I'm anticipating this whole
entire new lower low leg but I'm closing
out a quarter of the way of that whole
lower lower leg what Alex what do you
mean well look at this trade on the
weekly time frame this weekly trade on
the time frame we anticipate for it to
create a new lower low leg we have a
massive shift lower low lower high
retest this is the perfect price action
and it's literally confirming to you
that it's going to create the lower low
we're closing it 50% from the lower low
like we're closing our profits half
remember I analyze as a swing Trader I
just enter and execute the trade and
manage it as an intraday and day trader
but this is the most beautiful swing
trade you can ever possibly have this
trade will hit this low down here now
how long could that take 2 3 months sure
I will never hold a trade that long
because I just simply don't but I need
you guys to understand by set and
forgetting you're following your trading
plan you never want to cut your profit
short you want to maximize them how do
you maximize them
by set and forgetting so right now
obviously the trade is looking very well
we're having great momentum to begin the
week and if we were to decide to just
close this trade at the bottom of this
4our structure point right realistically
this structure point right here like we
would definitely surpass the go that we
would B for the week like right now
we're
up yeah that's crazy
cuz it's like last week bro we were like
doubting everything and just [__] cuz
I I was
dealing we having to explain this to you
guys last week when you guys were just
blowing me up close close close you guys
have to remember like I'm leading the
way with my strategy I'm explaining to
you guys how to trade with my strategy
only if you've been an experienced
Trader like me for 5 six years would you
understand what I'm looking at so it was
hard to like listen to people and then
do my own it was just hard to do
everything at the same time and I'm just
glad that I've become a stronger person
and I've been able to manage that stuff
and realize okay you know what I have to
stick to what I have to do last year at
this very point I cracked pop up the
clip of me cracking last year so I'm
going to leave social media for as long
as I feel like because you know this
whole challenge stuff I've been doing
this now
for 3 months and it's been very
stressful um I've given my off and
clearly in the last 2 3 weeks have just
been completely breaking my training
plan everything has just pretty much
gone down the drain and I'm going to
enter a dark mode but now this year I'm
stronger and I'm a completely different
person I'm glad I'm able to show this to
you guys so bro this doesn't stop look
at it like why would I want to close
this right now we're in like this is the
whole point of the move this momentum
this literal Trend continuation now when
this one starts having a reversal cuz I
actually got this question asked like oh
Alex how do you know when to stop your
profits when you're in the momentum move
great question and this is the answer so
when you're in this move when you have
this lower low this is literally
destined to have a lower high I don't
want to be part of that lower high cuz I
can then re-enter the trade where can I
decide how to stop it very easy when you
start seeing the 15minute structure
shift so that's why I told you this
Candlestick right here we had to wait
for it to close because if it would have
closed bullish and it would have start
actually heading to the upside
structurally now that trade is going to
have a reversal to here and then start
hiding to the downside since it Clos
bearish and everything after has been
bearish just very clear indication that
the momentum is going to keep going to
the downside as soon as I start seeing
some price action right around here on
the 15minute that it's going to reject
and then start having that pullback is
where I will immediately close that
position and take my profits at that
point because this pullback is just
needed same thing as up here when we had
this major lower low move I entered up
here I knew it was going to have a
pullback I just got emotional closed it
but lower low lower high lower low lower
high it's going to happen I can
literally draw this move right here look
let show you guys we have a lower low
and a lower high I'm just going to grab
this same move to right around here so
we technically to repeat this same move
we have that much more runway in this
trade before we have the pullback and
notice where the pullback is right
around the same level where we should be
having that retest so I don't know I
might make a decision very soon soon I
do want to close right at flat 200,000
[__] now we're at
198 so I can't look at this I'm just
supposed to look at this because this
will directly reflect what is going on
here so I know I'm preaching a little
bit but I need you guys to deeply
understand this it's more than just
reading the markets it's like really
getting it as a person getting it as a
Trader
so I feel like I poured everything out
there so stay tuned we're on our way
right now to Fort lauderale so you guys
have an idea it's about an hour away
from my home not because I'm going to
the beautiful beach of Fort lauderale or
the beautiful American women of Fort
Lauderdale it's to go see my
Bugatti [__]
NPC so we're on the way to Fort laale to
go see my broken
batti that has been broken down for 3
weeks why what because I decided to be
that guy and do some donuts in it and uh
not only did I just destroy the battery
by leaving it on overnight without even
knowing cuz since it's my first Bugatti
I don't know how to function and nobody
there's no handbook on how to use a
Bugatti you go on YouTube right now how
do you use a Bugatti no billionaire that
owns a Bugatti is going to make a
Bugatti video on how to use a Bugatti so
I have to figure [__] out myself so I
messed up the battery and I broke the
belt to the alternator don't ask me how
the car has a 1,000 miles it's brand new
and uh it's mission impossible to get
this go but we did at the Cuban High
Alia Miami
way and we got a belt from a Toyota Cora
and we put it on it so we're going to
see if we can withstand the 1600
horsepower from the Bugatti trade update
wait is wait oh my God that guy ran the
[__] out of that sh so did
I who's more Savage you or me all right
so trade up there boys we have
officially closed the trade
at
$200,000 you guys can see right here in
our trade history that we have
officially closed the trade now it's
exactly what I said this trade has so
much more downside potential but without
a lower high so we avoided this draw
down to Perfection we closed the trade
not at the lowest point you know we
could have closed at the bottom of those
Wicks but it's exactly what I
anticipated price is to have a retest to
retest this level of support and
resistance so then price can then
continue to head to the downside we
might add an entry very very soon on
this position right around here but
we're going to be like you know what
should we risk the extra cuz I won't
risk 100% I'll probably risk like 50k
because we surpassed to go for the week
but I don't know so I'm going to decide
later today cuz this is happening right
now at 5:00 right at the daily
Candlestick closure so if I show you the
daily time
frame bless you thanks dude you got to
say that a little bit faster sometimes
right usually do it three times you're
right see what I tell you this guy knows
me that was pretty accurate all right so
if the daily time frame closes with a
daily Wick like this then the next day
we're going to fill that daily Wick so
we definitely have another lower high
creating right now that if we get some
good price action tonight in session we
can easily catch that and catch the
trade make another 50 to 150k for now R
oh my God I'm just playing with them now
yeah oh my God what she saying say it
loud got a Bugatti would be fun
this so I don't know the the way I look
at it is like everything happens for a
reason
maybe I don't know I don't want to say
anything negative but maybe I drive the
Bugatti really fast some night and you
know something not great happens and
maybe it being down this long avoided
something like that so you know it does
suck on the short term but I think on
the long term it happens for the greater
good since we can't go see uh since we
can't take out the
Bugatti just came to look at a jet
potentially sometimes you got to just be
ready for anything see that that's an
old girl right there we want something
like that
black get him get
[Music]
him me
um so I go in real quick turn my $100
into
200k I told myself I would never walk
back into that place unless I am ready
to lose all the money that I go in with
[__] that and today I'm not okay with it
so for that very reason
not going in so sticking true to my word
I just want to uh all in on Blackjack
you
know but I'm good it looks nice
though welcome ladies and gentlemen well
[__] no good night ladies and gentlemen
trade update it is currently
12:45 in the morning it's about to be
1:00 a.m. right now we are in a new
position where now the account is up $35
gazillion dollar I'm kidding we're still
at the same exact spot still no trades
that we have added on to the challenge
so we did miss this new added position
on USD CAD as you guys can see pric has
actually had a retracement to the area
exactly how I anticipated price came
back retested the structure level and
now it looks like it's having a sell
down we literally pulled out right I
mean you know we had a little bit more
that we could have potentially gotten
but you know it's simply not worth it so
we got out at at the perfect area right
before this retracement we're looking to
add positions here but the session was
not the right session to be entering
this trade so for me to be interested in
adding a new position I would have to
wait for a retest here to then head to
the downside so I'm going to be waiting
for that lower high to then sell USD JPY
is giving us a perfect Daily Double top
potential rejection Candlestick we have
double Wicks at the top daily and
decision candle 4H hour is breaking and
retesting under this structure we're now
bearish now we're coming back to retest
round psychological level
14400 and then on the 1 hour time frame
it looks like we're coming back to
create this lower high cuz we're
creating higher high higher low high low
high shift structure so now this is
literally the exact point where I would
want to enter this trade like I would
literally want to enter this trade
obviously not right now I have to wait
for my engulfing Candlestick but this is
the area where I want to enter this tra
my stop loss would be right around here
let's call it 50 Pips and my take profit
could be all the way down here for a
quick smooth and easy one to six reward
like I hope you know if on this [__]
trade right here if I were to take this
trade and I risk 100% of the account
meaning 200,000 and I get the 1 to six
risk reward I will turn the
200k into $1.2 million
now should we do that right
now probably not cuz it would be
quite maybe we
should I think we
should let's just do it right now
everything on black everything on black
[__] it
ready no that's how you make an
emotional trading decision you have to
wait for your entry signal as of right
now there is no entry signal there is no
trade so we're going to be waiting for a
bearish engulfing Candlestick from this
Market to be interested in taking this
trade to the downside every other Market
Kai JPY EUR JPY a JPY
nzdjpy I'm not interested in any of
these markets they're not giving me the
price action that I want just looks ugly
USC JPY is the number one so basically
waiting for an engulfing to then sell
and then USD CAD waiting for little
pullback to then sell stay tuned Ted and
I'll see you in the morning good morning
ladies and gentlemen it is currently
10:38 in the morning and basically
following up exactly what I said
yesterday obviously no trades so far in
the account same exact
trades if we would have just continued
to set and forget in our position or at
a position like I mentioned yesterday
when we were on our way to go see the
Bugatti we would probably be up right
now half a million dollars when you're
trading with the Trend the whole point
is to set and forget price had a perfect
retest of this area of Interest price
then retested daily area of interest and
we had the daily Wick how many times
have I said that we are going to fill
the daily Wick a million times so this
is a perfect example of why we continue
to hold our position and we don't cut
our profit shorts when we're trading
with the trend I strongly believe this
has the ability to easily make it down
here to this low by the end of this week
it's just what the market move is doing
look at the weekly time frame retest
sell I like I said we cut our profits
halfway of the overall move but it is
what it is we he our goal for the week
next we have usdjpy which we are
actually very interested in entering
this trade very soon what I would need
to see though is for this daily time
frame to close like this I would need
for it to close with this double daily
doy because the next day I can
anticipate a push to the downside so for
right now I don't love this price action
on the 4H hour and I don't love it on
the 1 hour even though yes if I were to
enter if I would have entered we would
have obviously be in profit but if you
noticed yesterday we never got our entry
signal we never executed the trade CU
right now we are having what could be
the potential entry signal but I want to
wait for the daily Candlestick to close
in order for us to actually be
interested in this position so this
position is still very much active can
still very much happen but we're just
going to be waiting for a little bit
more price action all these other
markets I am not interested at all I'm
only interested in USD CAD or USD JPY
USD CAD is just gone she's a goner
there's nothing we can do the trade has
simply sailed its way we entered at the
perfect point up here and then we
re-entered at this point right here
there's nothing else we can do other
than just set and forget we can't scale
in at this point the trade is simply
good done the trade is just happening
there's nothing that we could do about
it now what we can do is just find a new
opportunity on this market and if you
were to ask me this price action here
looks very similar to this price action
here it's approaching an area of
interest in a 4-Hour bullish form
accumulation and then sell it's
approaching the area of interest in a 4H
hour bullish form accumulation and then
soell the only difference between this
and USD CAD is that this had a bit more
accumulation that is where USD JPY is
currently right now we're waiting for
that break from this point right here
obviously from that point right there
it's supposed to sell but this price
decided to have some liquidity pulls
before actually having the move right
now USD JPY we're at that very exact
same point so let's be very selective on
that and we'll update you guys so today
what mission do we have we have um we're
going to go look at a new boat I don't
know if we can show you everything it's
like supposed to be a surprise but you
guys are part of the series so we can
you know give a little bit of an Insight
but we're going to go look at a new boat
that's all I can
say all right so right now we're on our
way to go to the OH police oh [__] we're
about 37 minutes for the boat that we're
going to go see we're going to see how
much we can actually show you guys
without showing you what it is we want
it to be a surprise well I don't know if
I'm going to buy it yet I have to like
it first so on our way right now think
go see our new boat
strategically hiding behind
thear te you be hiding Alex why are you
hiding behind the car cuz I don't have a
license plate why don't you have a
license plate cuz when you're a
profitable Trader you do whatever the
[__] it's very smart to have a Han slice
that goes over your shoulders cuz like I
said this car is very too crash don't
know what you're doing and what what is
this like semi like does it what is got
so okay so there's a clutch that's only
for the first to get into first gear so
it's like a F1 car but they have a hand
clutch on F1 cars yeah um you use the
clutch to get into first and then after
that you don't use your uh and is it
supposed to be this soft or is it is it
what do you mean like the clutch or when
it turns on does it get harder no it's
it's very very soft like I feel like it
doesn't even engage
yeah
it's that's how it is for the race cars
it's a real touch soft it it it takes a
solid second to get used to that clch
though 0
to know that works intermittently that I
never fixed it is the shower does it
work it does it works sometimes and it
doesn't work I don't know why you can
get it for
5 like
500 right
now I wi him by [__] not me you'll
wire
[Music]
him oh no wait the actual the actual
strip is like way that way and then we
would have a ginormous [__]
untapped private airport that is
closed don't ask how we got here but we
got here and don't ask why yeah don't
ask why we're here Cuban
Colombian you know air strip air strip
boats boats cars
watches come to your own
confusion no no we're we're kidding
we're actually just trying to find a
[__] air strip so we can race the
cars
legally but how do we get in might be
illegal but all right ladies and
gentlemen back home into the office we
picked up our shipments we just
distribute it okay guys please it's a
joke this is our shipment right here and
um our shipment is actually getting
ready so before that I am actually just
just a little just a little bit annoyed
simply because I knew this was going to
happen we analyzed this and I said it a
gazillion times a billion times all you
had to do was set and forget which is
this trade right here this trade
absolutely
violated my takeprofit we close here for
a 1 to three for 70 Pips if I would have
continued to hold this position to the
point we are now we' get a 1 to7 for 144
Pips this account right now instead of
being at 200,000 we would easily be over
half a million dollars with one trade
from 40K why because we set and forget
like I've explained a million times
we're taking a trade at a daily area of
Interest we're rejecting from a daily
support and resistance we have to set
daily take profits this right here my
take my real take profit would have been
to that structure point right there cuz
it's the daily structure Point we've
body close under that this is easily
going to have a lower high and just
going to continue Plumbing into the
downside so for the next
analysis listen to me set and forget but
it's okay because luckily the next trade
is literally lining up right now now you
uh USD JPY we've had a daily bearish pin
bar confirmation with the liquidity pool
with that Wick above what we're going to
be waiting for price now to do is create
a little quick lower high and then sell
so this is actually looking very nice
very clean lower low I don't think this
could just keep going to the downside
without having a retest before heading
to the downside so we're going to wait
for this quick retest and uh we'll check
back in it is currently 6:53 in the
afternoon check back in right before
London session trade update boys it is
currently and I say boys because 99% of
the videos that watch this are meant aut
of testosterone on here kind of sus 600
p.m EST still no Trad in the account
everything exactly the same you're still
set of forgetting so you guys can see
here that USD CAD currently is having
the pullback exactly how we were
anticipating for price to do it which is
great because this is going to give us
some nice opportunities for next week to
actually be able to execute this Market
next we have USD JPY like I mentioned
we're going to break now and we're going
to retest and continue to head to the
upside don't love that bullish daily and
golf and Candlestick for a sell I've
seen this happen many many many times in
the past now we're going to wait for a
quick retest to then buy to the
upside that's it morning ladies and
gentlemen currently is
946 boring trade updates lately can't
even lie absolutely no trades into the
account the markets are doing literally
nothing so you guys can see here price
is just having a little bit of pullback
exactly what I anticipated had a
rejection nothing else that we can
expect from this market then we have USD
JPY which we are having the retest how
we wanted to but I'm not looking to
enter this trade just yet because again
keep in mind it is like basically Friday
Junior almost so there's only basically
one more session left in the market and
I'm not trying to get involved right now
I I don't know I don't want to be that
guy that wants a force a trade at the
end of the week especially when I hit my
goal for the week but this is a perfect
entry signal you can very easily enter
this trade right around here stop loss
right under it and then this could be a
quick take profit right here for a quick
one to two I don't like how the
structure went bearish CU you can see
higher high higher low high high higher
low higher high higher low higher high
lower low and now we're bearish 30
minute is bearish and 15 minute is
bearish the only way I will actually be
able to be interested in taking this
trade is once price breaks above that
structure level and then has a pullback
and then we can take the trade so for
now not interested in that one and gpusd
lastly didn't give us the retest how we
wanted to so we missed the
whole boring updates I know
but I don't could control the markets I
do control the markets no I don't I mean
I have a guy inside the markets that I
call I'm like yo I'm about to enter a
trade help me out and then you know
holding me a little bit of an edge I'm
kidding got to be lit though so now s
and forget let's see what today brings
it is currently 1:45 in the afternoon on
a Friday no more trades have been added
since literally the Monday of this week
I know it's been a boring challenge this
week I generally haven't done much I've
just been pretty much home yesterday I
slept for like 16 hours but this is a
perfect example of the trade idea that
we anticipated you react and adapt you
enter the next trade and then you avoid
a loss so let's start off with USD well
actually before we go to USD JPY let's
go to USD CAD so USD CAD is not having
the reaction from here as we anticipated
it is having a pullback which is really
good in my opinion because I think this
trade all of next week is just going to
have a massive push to the downside I
think the weekly time frame is closing
with this ginormous weekly Wick and that
is going to be a very good indication
for next week to open up and fill that
Wick and create a solid lower low on
this Market which is going to be
absolutely beautiful next going to be
usdjpy where yesterday we anticipated
for price to have a quick retest of this
level and then head to the upside to
then buy and that is quite exactly what
we did hit the takeprofit Zone we be
looking to get out for a 1 to 2.5 but
then this [__] happened honestly I'm
going to be 100% honest and 100%
transparent I would have lost this trade
why would you have lost well this is why
because I would have entered this trade
and you guys know I like to set and
forget and I would have continued to
modify my take profit and I would have
probably set one up here for one to four
for example and after seeing price
action like this after price creating a
higher high I would probably anticipate
for price to have a quick retest of this
structure level to then keep heading to
the upside but never in a million years
would I expect that one Candlestick
would just come in and do that you look
at it on the 15minute that is [__]
brutal that is news look at that like I
would see that price action I'm like
okay you know what great I'm going to go
take a shower go eat something and I
would come back 15 minutes
later with a [__] heart attack how
does this trade go from being up a one
to three almost
and then 15 minutes later
you that's brutal now you guys say well
you go to break even no you never go to
break even if last week was not a
perfect lesson for that I don't know
what else is so this would actually be a
losing trade for me if I would have
executed it simply because I would have
continued to set and forget because the
price action was so beautiful so we
avoided the loss earlier this week down
here at the breaking retest we never got
our entry then we missed this but it was
for the good because we would have
avoided this crazy ass loss next week
I'm going to definitely be interested in
selling this Market if it decides to
close like this because we still have 3
hours left in the daily time frame and
we all know how things can change
extremely fast next week I'll be looking
for retest so on and so forth so this
week we ended off for the 201,000 the
account no more trades let me actually
show them one second and you guys can
see we're up 21,000
and the trade history you guys can see
absolutely everything there
so no more trades in the account this is
a perfect example of the set and forget
strategy uh next week we're going to try
and turn these 200k into 400 to half
million and then next week we're going
to turn the half mil into a million boys
we are close we're almost there
literally last time I'm going to even
show you guys this look at this
literally this was about to be nearly 1
year ago that I blew the challenge and
that I simply broke my trading rules I
simply avoided all the lessons that I
was getting in front of me I was just
making continuous mistakes over and over
again you guys can see right here that
literally on October 6th 2023 doing this
now
for 3 months and it's so yeah literally
on October 6 is going to be about a year
so one basically one week away is going
to be is going to mark one year exactly
from when I last attempted The Challenge
and I was at the exact same point where
I am now I was just at like 300K and I
blew the challenge we're officially
blown the account we're about to hit
Margin Call right now that is not going
to happen this time I learned from my
mistakes and I am prepared for these
next weeks so we're two weeks away from
completing this Challenge and I know
we're going to do it all I can say is
join the set and forget community be
part of these calls that I do every
single Sunday where I literally shed it
before the during the after you guys saw
how I just did one this Sunday
completely for free let me show you guys
here humans we've been actually trading
things for thousands of let me just show
over here you guys can see how I did it
right here completely for free for an
hour and a half 70,000 people saw it in
4 days cuz I shared the before during
the after and I never really do it free
so that was the last Sunday swings that
I did for free for the rest of the
challenge until I complete it every
single Sunday swings where I share these
trades is in the link in description
below you guys will get access to my
whole entire strategy you guys will get
access to my private Discord private
events weekly calls with me live and my
psychology series all I have to do is
join the c foret community and you're
going to be able to potentially have
results just like these if you apply the
strategy correctly think about the
strategy like a weapon the set and
forget strategy is a ginormous machine
gun like a ginormous edit a ginormous
machine gun right here the biggest don't
show my feet I'm not wearing shoes so
the ginormous machine gun now if the
soldier that is holding the machine gun
is not equipped and skinny and he can't
even carry the weight of it the machine
gun has no use you have to be strong
built like
me to be ready to handle the machine gun
so that's what I do every single week I
train you to be ready to use this
machine gun and take it to battle which
are the markets and when you come here
to the markets you come here and you
simply go
edit edit the gun and edit the
noise but if you're not built and strong
to do that you simply have no use for
the gun so I I can say his Link in
description see you guys this Sunday
next week's going to be 200k to half a m
sad and
forget so we're going to end off this
week with the machine gun
example but we actually got one we got
one right now now this is what I mean
buy
machine my fingers on
there all right so you want to come in
here creep into my [__] balcony and
[__] on my balcony and not clean it
thought I forgot about look come here
look look that was you right there and
you are yet to pick it up think I forgot
no no no no no no no no I haven't
forgotten but you want to know what I'm
going to forgive
you just tell me one
thing what's going to happen next week
are we going to go
up or are we going to go down tell
me there's a lot of people watching me
give me the signal I'm taking you
outside tell your friends to not [__]
around here and leave [__] all over the
place all right tell your friends you
hear
me tell your friends okay got it got it
bet he learned this lesson